[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Where are we left here, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "we", "left", "here", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "When we were listening -- we're in court this morning and we were listening to the state's case, you know, we were all thinking, oh, you know, that's it.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "we", "were", "listening", "--", "we", "'re", "in", "court", "this", "morning", "and", "we", "were", "listening", "to", "the", "state", "'s", "case", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "all", "thinking", ",", "oh", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "She has such this multi-facetted kind of career that she was building for herself, but what kind of woman was she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "has", "such", "this", "multi-facetted", "kind", "of", "career", "that", "she", "was", "building", "for", "herself", ",", "but", "what", "kind", "of", "woman", "was", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Reeva was -- she was exceptional.", "answer_tokens": ["Reeva", "was", "--", "she", "was", "exceptional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "How did you hear that she had died?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "that", "she", "had", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "That's very hard.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "very", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "How would you sum up the atmosphere given the appalling circumstances of her death?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "sum", "up", "the", "atmosphere", "given", "the", "appalling", "circumstances", "of", "her", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "It was terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "When did Reeva tell you that she was dating Oscar Pistorius?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "Reeva", "tell", "you", "that", "she", "was", "dating", "Oscar", "Pistorius", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, I saw it in the -- in the news first, and that was about only two months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "saw", "it", "in", "the", "--", "in", "the", "news", "first", ",", "and", "that", "was", "about", "only", "two", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oscar Pistorius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "How would you describe the family reaction to him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "family", "reaction", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I think the family are devastated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "family", "are", "devastated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Reeva"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Any suggestion that it was a volatile relationship or anything about all that?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "suggestion", "that", "it", "was", "a", "volatile", "relationship", "or", "anything", "about", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "No, Piers, you know, we were all in shock that Reeva died the way she did.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "all", "in", "shock", "that", "Reeva", "died", "the", "way", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Do you or do the family think that is a possibility?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "or", "do", "the", "family", "think", "that", "is", "a", "possibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "You know something, Piers, I -- that is what in my heart I hope and wish is the truth because I would not like to think that my cousin suffered.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "something", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "--", "that", "is", "what", "in", "my", "heart", "I", "hope", "and", "wish", "is", "the", "truth", "because", "I", "would", "not", "like", "to", "think", "that", "my", "cousin", "suffered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And finally, Kim, how would you like Reeva to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", ",", "Kim", ",", "how", "would", "you", "like", "Reeva", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "For her sense of humor, for her kindness, her magical presence.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "her", "sense", "of", "humor", ",", "for", "her", "kindness", ",", "her", "magical", "presence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Where are you with this?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, obviously I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What evidentially have you seen which can be backed up by any apparent fact which actually says he did murder her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "evidentially", "have", "you", "seen", "which", "can", "be", "backed", "up", "by", "any", "apparent", "fact", "which", "actually", "says", "he", "did", "murder", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, let me start with the affidavit, and this is like a little inside dirty secret in the legal profession.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "start", "with", "the", "affidavit", ",", "and", "this", "is", "like", "a", "little", "inside", "dirty", "secret", "in", "the", "legal", "profession", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Piers, really?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, I mean let me come back to Alan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "let", "me", "come", "back", "to", "Alan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "NNS", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Vinnie, very quickly, finally, just tell me the one thing that you have heard which you believe points to his guilt as a cold- blooded murder?", "question_tokens": ["Vinnie", ",", "very", "quickly", ",", "finally", ",", "just", "tell", "me", "the", "one", "thing", "that", "you", "have", "heard", "which", "you", "believe", "points", "to", "his", "guilt", "as", "a", "cold-", "blooded", "murder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "He shot first and asked questions later is his explanation.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "shot", "first", "and", "asked", "questions", "later", "is", "his", "explanation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza", "Nancy"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Where were you when you hear the news about what Adam Lanza did at Sandy Hook School?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "about", "what", "Adam", "Lanza", "did", "at", "Sandy", "Hook", "School", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Piers, I was at work when I -- I had I heard the -- the, you know -- the ongoing coverage all day long, but I was at work when I found out about Adam Lanza and, sadly, my friend, Nancy, who I knew then, who was no longer with us.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "was", "at", "work", "when", "I", "--", "I", "had", "I", "heard", "the", "--", "the", ",", "you", "know", "--", "the", "ongoing", "coverage", "all", "day", "long", ",", "but", "I", "was", "at", "work", "when", "I", "found", "out", "about", "Adam", "Lanza", "and", ",", "sadly", ",", "my", "friend", ",", "Nancy", ",", "who", "I", "knew", "then", ",", "who", "was", "no", "longer", "with", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sandy Hook School"], "PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Was that your impression?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "impression", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I just -- you know, I knew she loved her son.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "knew", "she", "loved", "her", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What kind of woman was Nancy Lanza?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "woman", "was", "Nancy", "Lanza", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "She was a wonderful friend.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "a", "wonderful", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Why would she feel the need for all that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "she", "feel", "the", "need", "for", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I don't know that it was that she felt she needed them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "it", "was", "that", "she", "felt", "she", "needed", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "And what does that tell you, I guess, about the problems with dealing with mental health perhaps in relation to gun violence?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "that", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "about", "the", "problems", "with", "dealing", "with", "mental", "health", "perhaps", "in", "relation", "to", "gun", "violence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Well, as far as Nancy goes, she was -- you know, she was trained in how to use a gun and in proper gun safety.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "far", "as", "Nancy", "goes", ",", "she", "was", "--", "you", "know", ",", "she", "was", "trained", "in", "how", "to", "use", "a", "gun", "and", "in", "proper", "gun", "safety", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What was your reaction to what Vice President Biden had to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "Vice", "President", "Biden", "had", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, I was rather shocked that he said such a thing because basically I've taught about 7,000 women how to shoot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "rather", "shocked", "that", "he", "said", "such", "a", "thing", "because", "basically", "I", "'ve", "taught", "about", "7,000", "women", "how", "to", "shoot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What would your response be to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "response", "be", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, I agree with him that I think an AR-15 is not something that the normal, average citizen should have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "with", "him", "that", "I", "think", "an", "AR-15", "is", "not", "something", "that", "the", "normal", ",", "average", "citizen", "should", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "When you heard Joe Biden say what he said, what did you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "Joe", "Biden", "say", "what", "he", "said", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, as you know, I am a gun owner, and I do own a shotgun.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "I", "am", "a", "gun", "owner", ",", "and", "I", "do", "own", "a", "shotgun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "This one goes in your bra?", "question_tokens": ["This", "one", "goes", "in", "your", "bra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "This goes into your bra.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "goes", "into", "your", "bra", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Are you content that more and more women buy weapons through this kind of direct marketing that they're like the next Chanel handbag?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "content", "that", "more", "and", "more", "women", "buy", "weapons", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "direct", "marketing", "that", "they", "'re", "like", "the", "next", "Chanel", "handbag", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "UIGLEY: No.", "answer_tokens": ["UIGLEY", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "What do you say to people that believe that is the only solution?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "people", "that", "believe", "that", "is", "the", "only", "solution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I don't agree that's the answer either, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "agree", "that", "'s", "the", "answer", "either", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Patrick, how has it been dealing with his loss?", "question_tokens": ["Patrick", ",", "how", "has", "it", "been", "dealing", "with", "his", "loss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "It's -- it's a mixed sort of bag of feelings because, you know, the three of us, we're the best of friends.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "mixed", "sort", "of", "bag", "of", "feelings", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "three", "of", "us", ",", "we", "'re", "the", "best", "of", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "How do you feel when you hear him talking?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "hear", "him", "talking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, it's that wonderful bittersweet.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "that", "wonderful", "bittersweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]